Fatemeh Rezwani

Frontend Developer (JavaScript, React) with **3+ years** of experience in developing websites. I have worked on different projects ranging from small personal websites to larger, more complex web applications using JavaScript and JavaScript Frameworks like ReactJs, and VueJs.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Marzia School (Teaching Web Developing for Afghan Girls)

Remote - Mentor - Nov 2022 - PRESENT

HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Git

- I'm currently working on an online coding course to help Afghan Girls to get improve.
- Teaching Fundamentals of Web Designing by Apparat Channel like YouTube.

Green Vision Engineering Company (Managed a Startup and Digital Marketing)

Afghanistan, Herat – Project Manager - Nov 2020 – Jun 2021

- Modified the structure and managed the website as a Start-Up in this company called (Khaneh). it was an Online _Shop and Real State Website developed by Reacts & Redux, and Node.Is.
- It was the first startup that provided people in Afghanistan with experiences in using websites
 and applications to buy, rent, and sell homes, apartments, or anything they need During the
 coronavirus.
- Collaborated with the **UX/UI** design teams to improve the website.
- Problem resolving and finding solutions for the Start-Up with the Development Team.

Asooda Award company (Intern)

Afghanistan, Herat – Frontend Engineer - Jun 2020 - Mar 2021

Java Script, CSS, Bootstrap, React, Redux

- Member of the Afghan Girls Code team, working for peace and women projects.
- Worked on many mini projects to improve my skills in Software Engineering.

Bests in Tech_(Intern)

Afghanistan, Herat – Web Developer - Jul 2019 - Mar 2020

- Collaborated with the UX/UI design teams to improve a website for the Company.
- Conducted a custom website and Admin Dashboard for the Electronic online shop using Vue.Is and Node.Is.

EDUCATION

Herat University, Computer Science Faculty (Not Graduated, Bachelor)

Afghanistan, Herat

2017-2021

Code to Inspire, (Full Stack Engineering)

Afghanistan, Herat

Nov 2019 - Mar 2021

Email: azadehrezwani@gmail.com Phone: (+98)9154518166

Phone: (+98)9154518166 LinkedIn: LinkedIn GitHub: GitHub

STACK

Proficient: JavaScript, Bootstrap, Tailwind, Css, Vue, React, Redux, Git

Experienced: NodeJs, MongoDB, PHP, SQL, NPM, Yarn, Material UI

LANGUAGES

English B1, Intermediate German A1, beginner Dari native

CERTIFICATES & AWARDS:

Free Code Camp

29Dec 2023

Code to Inspire Nov2019- Mar 2021

ITCH

Jun 2018 - Sep 2018

PROJECTS

Personal Web:

Developed a personal Web Page with ReactJs. **GitHub:** Click Here

Admin Panel:

Developed a Dashboard to Add, Remove, and Update products in a Stuck.

GitHub: Click Here

Online-Shop:

Create an Online shop with React and Redux.

GitHub: Click Here